<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Μοντέλα αστικής εξάπλωσης και παρακολούθηση με τηλεπισκόπηση - Δημοσιέσεις-Συνέδρια</title><link href="https://phd.geographer.gr/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://phd.geographer.gr/feeds/demosieseis-sunedria.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://phd.geographer.gr/</id><updated>2021-01-24T00:00:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>Δημοσιέσεις-Συνέδρια</title><link href="https://phd.geographer.gr/publications.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-01-24T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2021-01-24T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Λεωνίδας Λιάκος</name></author><id>tag:phd.geographer.gr,2021-01-24:/publications.html</id><content type="html">&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stathakis, Demetris, Leonidas Liakos, and Pavlos Baltas. 2021. “Covid-19 Pandemic Assessment by Night-Lights.” In IEEE International Geoscience and Remote Sensing Symposium (IGARSS) 2021. Brussels, Belgium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stathakis, Demetris, Leonidas Liakos, Vassilis Tselios, and Pavlos Baltas. 2021. “Night Light as an Indicator of the Pandemic’s Impact on Economic Activity in Touristic Areas.” In 60th ERSA Congress Territorial Futures – Visions and Scenarios to Cope with Megatrends in a Changing Europe. Bolzano-Bozen, Italy, 24-27 August 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stathakis, Demetris, Leonidas Liakos, and Pavlos Baltas. 2021. “Medium Temporal Scale Night-Lights Data for Detecting Abnormal Events.” In NightLights Virtual Workshop 2021. Virtual Event: Alba Orbital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stathakis, Demetris N., and Leonidas Liakos. 2020. “Time Series Formation Based on VIIRS 24h Data.” In Remote Sensing Technologies and Applications in Urban Environments V, edited by Nektarios Chrysoulakis, Thilo Erbertseder, and Ying Zhang, 17. Online Only, United Kingdom: SPIE. doi:10.1117/12.2574346.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stathakis, Demetris, and Leonidas Liakos. 2020. “Median Shift Lunar Correction for VIIRS.” IEEE Geoscience and Remote Sensing Letters, 1–5. doi:10.1109/LGRS.2020.3007965.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stathakis, Demetris, Pavlos Baltas, and Leonidas Liakos. 2019. “Preprocessing Very High Temporal Resolution Night-Lights Data For Noise Removal.” In 39th Annual EARSeL Symposium. Salzburg, Austria.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stathakis, Demetris, and Leonidas Liakos. 2019. “Further Adjustment of the Defense Meteorological Satellite Program-Operational Linescan System Using Radar Data.” Journal of Applied Remote Sensing 13 (03): 034507/1-9. doi:10.1117/1.JRS.13.034507.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stathakis, Demetris, and Leonidas Liakos. 2019. “VIIRS Lunar Radiance Removal by Dark Object Subtraction.” In IGARSS 2019 - IEEE International Geoscience and Remote Sensing Symposium, 6380–6383. Yokohama, Japan: IEEE. doi:10.1109/IGARSS.2019.8898906.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stathakis, Demetris, and Leonidas Liakos. 2018. “An Improved DMSP/OLS Times Series Based on Adjusted-Data.” In 38th Annual EARSeL Symposium, Earth Observation Supporting Sustainability Research. Chania, Crete, Greece.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stathakis, Demetris N., Leonidas Liakos, Christos Chalkias, and Maria Pafi. 2018. “A Photopollution Index Based on Weighted Cumulative Visibility to Night Lights.” In Remote Sensing Technologies and Applications in Urban Environments III, edited by Nektarios Chrysoulakis, Thilo Erbertseder, and Ying Zhang, 3. Berlin, Germany: SPIE. doi:10.1117/12.2500212.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><category term="Δημοσιέσεις-Συνέδρια"></category></entry></feed>